http://www.raceschool.com/privacy-statement

HomeOur Courses
Performance DrivingSpecialty CoursesCorporate OutingsUpcoming EventsCalendar of CoursesDocs & ResourcesCars & Tracks
Choose a Car
Supercharged Scion TCScion FR-S Race CarDrive Your Own CarChoose a Track
Willow Spring Raceway--Photo & Video GalleryAbout
About FAST LANEOur InstructorsDirectionsFAQPrintable DocsContactThank You 2019 Discount
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, FAST LANE have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information.
The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
FAST LANE is committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Powered by ConduireMarketing.com
Upcoming Courses
DEC
20
High Speed EVOC (Emergency Vehicle Operations Course)
Are you Fast Enough? Call Us Today!
Performance DrivingSpecialty CoursesCorporate OutingsUpcoming EventsCalendar of CoursesDocs & ResourcesCars & Tracks
Choose a Car
Supercharged Scion TCScion FR-S Race CarDrive Your Own CarChoose a Track
Willow Spring Raceway--Photo & Video GalleryAbout
About FAST LANEOur InstructorsDirectionsFAQPrintable DocsContactThank You 2019 Discount
